https://www.kanuga.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Kanuga Conferences, Inc. operates http://www.kanuga.org (the “Site”). This page informs you of our privacy policy regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.
HOW WE USE INFORMATION
Kanuga Conferences, Inc. uses your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE
While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name (“Personal Information”). Through our secure server, we may also collect personally identifiable information while you complete your order, such as name, shipping and billing addresses, phone number, email address, and payment information. We will never share, rent, or sell your Personal Information.
DATA
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze your activity on our site in order to improve the customer and user experience.
If you leave a review of our product on a third-party site or email us/mail us directly with a review of the product, we reserve the right to publish that review in a portion or entirety on our Site or social media properties. If you submit user content such as photo, video, or audio that includes Kanuga Conferences, Inc. products, we may republish this content on our Site or social media properties. We will never disclose your full name associated with your review or content without your permission.
COMMUNICATIONS
We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that you opt in to receive on our website before or during the checkout process. We may also use your Personal Information to contact you with transaction-related communications, such as emails regarding the confirmation and shipment of your order. You have the option to opt out of receiving promotional or marketing materials at any time.
COOKIES
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.
SECURITY
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
This Privacy Policy is effective as of October 3, 2016 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.
We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.
CONTACT US
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us: webmaster@kanuga.org.
Sign-up for Kanuga’s Email Newsletter:
©2020 Kanuga Conferences Inc., All Rights Reserved.
Sitemap   |   Privacy Policy
Get Directions
